I am delighted to be here, and I'm particularly delighted to be here on this occasion.
We meet at a college noted for knowledge, in a city noted for progress,
in a state noted for strength, and we stand in need of all three.
For we meet in an hour of change and challenge, in a decade of hope and fear, in an age of both knowledge and ignorance.
The greater our knowledge increases, the greater our ignorance unfolds.
Despite the striking fact that most of the scientists that the world has ever known are alive and working today,
despite the fact that this nation's own scientific manpower is doubling every 12 years
in a rate of growth more than three times that of our population as
a whole,
despite that,
the very